[{"answer": "Well, it was a horrific day.", "docId": "130320pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "What do you think needs to be done?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "I think it may help.", "docId": "130320pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "Do you think that if America had seen what you saw there would be any doubt about banning assault weapons?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "You know, I heard the president say they deserve a vote.", "docId": "130320pmt", "aSentId": 94, "question": "Why is it so important that there should be one?", "qSentId": 93}, {"answer": "I respect the Second Amendment.", "docId": "130320pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "What do you say to that?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "Yes, sir.", "docId": "130320pmt", "aSentId": 125, "question": "Actually I think you've got two Purple Hearts, am I right?", "qSentId": 124}, {"answer": "Background checks.", "docId": "130320pmt", "aSentId": 141, "question": "Of the three planks, really, of what Dianne Feinstein, the senator, is trying to push through, assault weapons, background checks, and the magazine, which of those things that do you feel strongest about?", "qSentId": 140}, {"answer": "I think the background checks are very important.", "docId": "130320pmt", "aSentId": 143, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 142}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "130320pmt", "aSentId": 172, "question": "Who takes possession of those weapons for the short term until it's decided who they should go to?", "qSentId": 171}, {"answer": "Well, certainly, on the surface, it is.", "docId": "130320pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "And that's the point of this, isn't it?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "Mr. Morgan, again, I don't think that there's any ability for -- I or my officers or other officers armed around the state to determine if a magazine that comes into our inspection was acquired before or after the ban.", "docId": "130320pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "Sheriff, are you -- are you saying you're not going to even try and enforce the law?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "And you're right.", "docId": "130320pmt", "aSentId": 253, "question": "At Sandy Hook, had he had 100 bullet magazine, he could have killed a lot more in the same period of time, right?", "qSentId": 252}, {"answer": "If I thought that was the fact, yes, sir.", "docId": "130320pmt", "aSentId": 268, "question": "And I would also like you to answer the point, if it saves one life of one child in a future mass shooting in your state, even in the area that you're the sheriff, isn't it worth it?", "qSentId": 267}, {"answer": "I think there's a -- I think there's a major concern which I concur with.", "docId": "130320pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "Who is going to miss 30, 40, 50 bullet magazines?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "I say that it's our responsibility to enforce the law, whatever it is.", "docId": "130320pmt", "aSentId": 296, "question": "What do you say to that?", "qSentId": 295}, {"answer": "There's no question, Piers, it's been obvious to the world, not just to these two leaders, that they've had a very frosty and somewhat unfriendly relationship.", "docId": "130320pmt", "aSentId": 329, "question": "But underneath all that, what is the reality of the state of the relationship between America and Israel right now?", "qSentId": 328}, {"answer": "Not much, which is part of the issue.", "docId": "130320pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "What do we really know about what may have happened here?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "No, it isn't.", "docId": "130320pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "Now there is so much tension all over the region, it's no longer just about Israel and Palestine, is it?", "qSentId": 369}, {"answer": "Well, it will be discussed in the morning.", "docId": "130320pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "And is that going to be discussed over the next couple of days?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "130320pmt", "aSentId": 396, "question": "How crucial is this going to be, this part of the debate?", "qSentId": 395}, {"answer": "I don't know all of the issues, because I don't follow them in nearly as much detail as when I myself was there.", "docId": "130320pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "I mean, do you not think they should, at the very least, be pushing forward to a vote, so that everyone can see who is in favor and who is against?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "I am very optimistic.", "docId": "130320pmt", "aSentId": 467, "question": "Are you remotely optimistic?", "qSentId": 466}, {"answer": "No, I don't.", "docId": "130320pmt", "aSentId": 495, "question": "Do you agree with that?", "qSentId": 494}, {"answer": "Well, we did a poll on that.", "docId": "130320pmt", "aSentId": 515, "question": "Are you optimistic that within five years there could be a peace deal?", "qSentId": 514}, {"answer": "Well, if the Palestinians sit down and negotiate, the Israelis will make a very generous offer, as they did in 2000, 2001 and 2007.", "docId": "130320pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "Alan?", "qSentId": 527}, {"answer": "The way we stop this is we have built this new product and platform, Blackberry 10, because we knew we had to come up with something really exciting and new.", "docId": "130320pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "How are you going to stop the migration, which has been going on now for quite some time, of your product to Apple and indeed to Samsung and Android?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "No, I think with Z-10 coming to market, I think they are falling behind in terms of the user interface.", "docId": "130320pmt", "aSentId": 604, "question": "Or were you hoping they're outdated?", "qSentId": 603}, {"answer": "The single best way is, first, the user interface we talked about.", "docId": "130320pmt", "aSentId": 622, "question": "What is the single best way you are going do hook them back with these new things?", "qSentId": 621}]